<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <copyright>Copyright (c) 2025 Yahoo Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright>
        <description>Latest Financial News for AAPL</description>
        <image>
            <height>45</height>
            <link>http://finance.yahoo.com/q/h?s=AAPL</link>
            <title>Yahoo! Finance: AAPL News</title>
            <url>https://s.yimg.com/rz/stage/p/yahoo_finance_en-US_h_p_finance_2.png</url>
            <width>144</width>
        </image>
        <item>
            <description>Apple lacks the growth to outperform Nvidia or Microsoft.  Microsoft's cloud computing division will propel it higher, but other divisions are holding it back.  Nvidia's massive growth is unheard of for a company of its size.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5623217b-3a21-38b8-b5be-ff0a23e2a440</guid>
            <link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2025/06/10/best-3-trillion-stock-to-buy-right-now-apple-micro/?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Best $3 Trillion Stock to Buy Right Now: Apple, Microsoft, or Nvidia?</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Buffett loves Apple's sticky ecosystem of consumer products, but Apple is expensive today.  Amazon's AI business presents massive opportunties, and the company's stock is trading at an attractive price.  Two of the top AI companies today are also two of the stocks in the Berkshire Hathaway portfolio.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">06da42cf-ef36-3f4e-8922-1b963008f15c</guid>
            <link>https://www.fool.com/investing/2025/06/10/apple-vs-amazon-which-warren-buffet-ai-stock-is-th/?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple vs. Amazon: Which Warren Buffet AI Stock Is the Better Buy Today?</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>What happened in markets yesterday: Export controls were at the top of the trade agenda. As U.S. and Chinese delegates met in London, American negotiators were expected to press Xi Jinping’s representatives to speed up exports of rare-earth minerals and magnets.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">19b68743-5cff-3334-84b2-b06f60cdfd4b</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/19b68743-5cff-3334-84b2-b06f60cdfd4b/heard-on-the-street%3A-warner.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 06:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Heard on the Street: Warner Discovery Splitting Up</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Apple’s flagship annual showcase has fallen flat as the iPhone maker fails to allay concerns that it is falling behind on artificial intelligence.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a1831750-b5de-397e-94a4-76806421bf15</guid>
            <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-ai-event-falls-flat-050000646.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple’s AI event falls flat as iPhone maker struggles</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>你的iPhone系统即将改头换面。苹果公司iOS 26将推出“液态玻璃”(Liquid Glass)操作系统设计，这是多年来最大规模的一次视觉革新。《华尔街日报》科技作家Joanna Stern带你一览在苹果全球开发者大会(WWDC 2025)官宣的重大更新。封面图片制作：Paige Money</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c8987e75-956e-3d5e-960b-eee294222342</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ios-26-visual-intelligence-040100329.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>苹果iOS 26重大更新一览：液态玻璃、Visual Intelligence和其他亮点</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) is poised to unveil a groundbreaking software design, dubbed “Liquid Glass,” at its upcoming Worldwide Developers Conference. Bloomberg’s Mark Gurman, in his latest weekly “Power On" report revealed that, the innovative ...</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">df85d201-fdd5-3d6a-b8fb-e69619564792</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apples-liquid-glass-interface-set-013113958.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 01:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple's Liquid Glass Interface Set To Revolutionize iOS 26, Hints At 20th Anniversary iPhone</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Apple is overhauling all of its devices' operating systems. It's a process that's been years in the making.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">09982677-aa92-438c-a069-f89e6778e0c3</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apples-software-makeover-was-years-in-the-making-010435692.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 01:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple’s software makeover was years in the making</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>The iPhone maker releases live language-translation capabilities and a broad software redesign. Some AI upgrades remain delayed.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1d795d08-c224-37c2-9d9d-cd31fab6396f</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/1d795d08-c224-37c2-9d9d-cd31fab6396f/apple-unveils-array-of-new.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple Unveils Array of New Software, but AI Comeback Remains Far Off</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Your iPhone is about to look a lot different.  Apple just announced iOS 26, featuring a new “liquid glass” design, smarter calling tools and more.  At Monday’s Worldwide Developers Conference keynote,  Apple  announced enhancements throughout its system apps and a new software look called “Liquid Glass,” coming soon to compatible iPhones, iPads, Apple Watches, Macs and other devices.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5fa18fd6-b35d-3056-be79-3b044e1e0efb</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/5fa18fd6-b35d-3056-be79-3b044e1e0efb/the-best-new-features-coming.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>The Best New Features Coming to Your iPhone, iPad and Mac (and What’s Missing)</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Your iPhone is about to look a lot different. Apple just announced iOS 26, featuring a new “liquid glass” design, smarter calling tools and more. WSJ’s Joanna Stern breaks down the biggest updates from Monday’s Worldwide Developers Conference.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f2192e90-b8bf-3acd-adcd-8acea99be9a2</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/ios-26-five-top-features-232200586.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 23:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>iOS 26 First Look: Liquid Glass, Visual Intelligence and Other Features</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Market Domination Overtime hosts Josh Lipton and Julie Hyman take a look at the top stories to watch on Tuesday, June 10. More earnings reports will be released tomorrow, including from Dave &amp; Buster's (PLAY) and GameStop (GME). GameStop will report its first quarter results after the bell, coming as the company expands into crypto with more than 4,700 bitcoin (BTC-USD) added to its balance sheet. The NFIB Small Business Optimism Index for the month of May will be released in the morning. Economists expect the number to hold steady from April at 95.8. Apple's (AAPL) Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) will continue into day two in Cupertino, California. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination Overtime here.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8b287477-ac5e-3b96-a39b-9b21eecd0753</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/gamestop-earnings-small-business-optimism-230000370.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>GameStop earnings, small business optimism: What to Watch</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Tony Wang, T. Rowe Price, Science &amp; Tech Fund, Portfolio Manager speaking with Romaine Bostick and Alix Steel about Apple's WWDC and AI apps.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3cbde204-f042-3724-ae70-956a3a059024</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-encourage-ai-apps-portfolio-215950605.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple Should Encourage AI Apps, Portfolio Manager Says</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Daniel Flax, Neuberger Berman, Senior Research Analyst speaks with Romaine Bostick and Alix Steel about Apple's WWDC.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c1a47ede-b792-32b6-a0a2-75ba69be768c</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-wwdc-ai-competition-stay-215540014.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple WWDC: AI Competition to Stay Fierce, Analyst Says</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>We saw no new trade deals made today, though market participants remain positive that they will be forthcoming.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4864067b-57a9-35b4-b12d-dc176b3b4ad8</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/markets-flat-no-economic-trade-215200472.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Markets Flat on No Economic or Trade News; Apple Flops at WWDC</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Apple's iPadOS 26 makes its tablet line far more useful.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6bbc9955-88b9-4d49-9791-e1dd61e007d4</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apples-ipad-is-about-to-get-a-lot-more-useful-213640019.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple’s iPad is about to get a lot more useful</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>At this year's Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC 25), Apple announced a slew of updates to its operating systems, services, and software, including a new look it dubbed "Liquid Glass" and a rebranded naming convention. Apple was notably quiet on one highly anticipated product: a more personalized, AI-powered Siri, which it first introduced at last year's conference. Apple's SVP of Software Engineering, Craig Federighi, only gave the Siri update a brief mention during the keynote address, say</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">320e5a02-5b46-3843-af6b-b1afb76c4eeb</guid>
            <link>https://techcrunch.com/2025/06/09/still-no-ai-powered-more-personalized-siri-from-apple-at-wwdc-25/?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Still no AI-powered, 'more personalized' Siri from Apple at WWDC 25</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Tesla trades lower ahead of the possible launch of its robo-taxi service this week in Austin, Texas, while Apple’s annual Worldwide Developers Conference begins Monday.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">90272a67-3d8a-3216-b5ef-2933a54b260f</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/90272a67-3d8a-3216-b5ef-2933a54b260f/these-stocks-moved-the-most.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>These Stocks Moved the Most Today: Tesla, Apple, Robinhood, AppLovin, Warner Bros., Nvidia, Qualcomm, and More</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>Apple (AAPL) CEO Tim Cook delivered the keynote at the company's 2025 WWDC, unveiling changes to the iPhone maker's software system, iPad advancements, and some updates on artificial intelligence (AI). Creative Strategies CEO and principal analyst Ben Bajarin joins Market Domination with Josh Lipton to share his takeaways from the event. To watch more expert insights and analysis on the latest market action, check out more Market Domination here.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b5fcc609-748e-3fb3-bdff-489a1d3cb29a</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/biggest-surprise-apple-wwdc-isnt-202926140.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>This was the 'biggest surprise' of Apple WWDC, and it isn't AI</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>"Siri is clueless and doesn't work," Ross Gerber, president and CEO of Gerber Kawasaki Wealth and Investment Management, says while discussing Apple's WWDC 2025. Speaking on "Bloomberg The Close," Gerber also says Steve Jobs would call Apple's new products "garbage."</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f32786fd-339b-35ad-b14f-6b97213dbf64</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/video/apple-isnt-even-ai-party-202438176.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple Isn't Even at the AI Party, Ross Gerber Says</title>
        </item>
        <item>
            <description>U.S. consumer plans to buy new Apple iPhones have fallen to their lowest level in five years, according to a semiannual survey.</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">88d15940-f8f1-3030-9c75-8a90d1c30f4e</guid>
            <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/88d15940-f8f1-3030-9c75-8a90d1c30f4e/apple-iphone-purchase-intent.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
            <title>Apple iPhone Purchase Intent Falls To 5-Year Low</title>
        </item>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 07:56:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <link>http://finance.yahoo.com/q/h?s=AAPL</link>
        <title>Yahoo! Finance: AAPL News</title>
    </channel>
</rss>
